New York Civil Liberties Union; Records apap331
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- NYCLU Website, 1998 December 5 - 2017 June 3; 1; 715 captures
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 March 9
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 March 10
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 March 15
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 March 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 March 22
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 March 29
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 March 31
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 April 3
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 April 3
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 April 4
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 April 5
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 April 8
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 April 12
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 April 15
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 April 22
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 April 26
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 April 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 May 3
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 May 10
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 May 17
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 May 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 May 25
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 June 11
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 June 26
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 June 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 June 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 July 2
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 July 14
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 July 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 July 27
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 August 3
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 August 4
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 August 10
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 August 17
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 August 19
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 August 21
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 August 24
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 August 31
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 September 5
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 September 7
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 September 14
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 September 16
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 September 21
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 September 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 October 1
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 October 1
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 October 6
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 October 15
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 October 18
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 November 5
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 November 8
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 November 9
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 November 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 November 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 December 11
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 December 13
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2015 December 22
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 January 11
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 January 19
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 January 25
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 January 26
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 February 4
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 February 8
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 February 9
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 February 10
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 February 12
  - not present, 2016 February 12
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 February 16
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 February 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 March 3
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 March 10
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 March 16
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 March 24
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 March 29
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 April 9
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 April 9
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 April 22
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 April 23
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 April 25
  - not present, 2016 May 13
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 May 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 May 26
    crawl: 214791
    Crawl Rules
    Limit host twitter.com to 1000 documents
    Limit host upload.wikimedia.org to 1000 documents
    Limit host en.wikipedia.org to 1000 documents
    Crawl Times
    start_date: 2016-05-26T14:53:30Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-26T14:53:30Z
    last_resumption: None
    processing_end_date: 2016-05-26T16:05:22Z
    end_date: 2016-05-26T15:53:59Z
    elapsed_ms: 3616451
    Crawl Types
    type: TEST_SAVED
    recurrence_type: NONE
    pdfs_only: False
    test: True
    Crawl Limits
    time_limit: 3600
    document_limit: None
    byte_limit: None
    crawl_stop_requested: None
    Crawl Results
    status: FINISHED_TIME_LIMIT
    discovered_count: 6340
    novel_count: 4471
    duplicate_count: 723
    resumption_count: 0
    queued_count: 1146
    downloaded_count: 5194
    download_failures: 0
    warc_revisit_count: 723
    warc_url_count: 5187
    total_data_in_kbs: 377382
    duplicate_bytes: 13335053
    warc_compressed_bytes: 211623060
    Crawl Technical Details
    doc_rate: 1.44
    kb_rate: 104.0
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 May 26
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 May 26
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 May 26
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 May 27
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 May 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 May 31
    crawl: 215649
    start_date: 2016-05-31T19:45:51Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-31T19:45:51Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-06-03T20:06:44Z
    end_date: 2016-06-03T19:46:26Z
    elapsed_ms: 259225543
    type: MONTHLY
    recurrence_type: MONTHLY
    test: False
    time_limit: 259200
    discovered_count: 35405
    novel_count: 25802
    duplicate_count: 3914
    queued_count: 5689
    downloaded_count: 29716
    download_failures: 8
    warc_revisit_count: 3914
    warc_url_count: 29706
    total_data_in_kbs: 6232003
    duplicate_bytes: 290062524
    warc_compressed_bytes: 3184879336
    doc_rate: 0.11
    kb_rate: 24.0
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 May 31
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 May 31
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 May 31
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 June 4
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 June 15
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 June 22
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 June 30
    crawl: 222955
    start_date: 2016-06-30T19:46:03Z
    original_start_date: 2016-06-30T19:46:03Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-07-03T19:59:43Z
    end_date: 2016-07-03T19:46:24Z
    elapsed_ms: 259216278
    discovered_count: 40792
    novel_count: 21934
    duplicate_count: 13202
    queued_count: 5656
    downloaded_count: 35136
    warc_revisit_count: 13184
    warc_url_count: 35122
    total_data_in_kbs: 6437329
    duplicate_bytes: 5700503648
    warc_compressed_bytes: 319862654
    doc_rate: 0.14
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 June 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 June 30
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 June 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 July 12
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 July 30
    crawl: 228055
    start_date: 2016-07-30T19:45:59Z
    original_start_date: 2016-07-30T19:45:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-08-02T23:35:42Z
    end_date: 2016-08-02T20:14:01Z
    elapsed_ms: 260857522
    discovered_count: 1172724
    novel_count: 267392
    duplicate_count: 13801
    queued_count: 891531
    downloaded_count: 281193
    download_failures: 10
    warc_revisit_count: 13749
    warc_url_count: 281154
    total_data_in_kbs: 21925334
    duplicate_bytes: 6569359411
    warc_compressed_bytes: 842149127
    doc_rate: 1.08
    kb_rate: 84.0
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 July 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 July 30
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 July 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 August 2
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 August 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 August 27
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 August 30
    crawl: 233563
    Limit host facebook.com to 500 documents
    Ignore Robots.txt for nyclu.org (last updated 2016-08-25)
    start_date: 2016-08-30T19:46:33Z
    original_start_date: 2016-08-30T19:46:33Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-09-02T20:01:46Z
    end_date: 2016-09-02T19:47:17Z
    elapsed_ms: 259234796
    discovered_count: 34358
    novel_count: 16736
    duplicate_count: 12271
    queued_count: 5351
    downloaded_count: 29007
    warc_revisit_count: 12246
    warc_url_count: 28978
    total_data_in_kbs: 6250821
    duplicate_bytes: 5708867960
    warc_compressed_bytes: 239823251
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 August 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 August 30
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 August 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 September 9
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 September 11
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 September 18
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 September 19
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 September 30
    crawl: 239799
    start_date: 2016-09-30T19:45:52Z
    original_start_date: 2016-09-30T19:45:52Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-10-03T20:02:23Z
    end_date: 2016-10-03T19:46:48Z
    elapsed_ms: 259247289
    discovered_count: 67365
    novel_count: 31833
    duplicate_count: 24636
    queued_count: 10896
    downloaded_count: 56469
    download_failures: 12
    warc_revisit_count: 24602
    warc_url_count: 56456
    total_data_in_kbs: 11028431
    duplicate_bytes: 9835935952
    warc_compressed_bytes: 797009685
    doc_rate: 0.22
    kb_rate: 42.0
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 September 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 September 30
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 September 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 October 7
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 October 12
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 October 14
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 October 30
    crawl: 245831
    start_date: 2016-10-30T19:45:58Z
    original_start_date: 2016-10-30T19:45:58Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-11-02T20:35:59Z
    end_date: 2016-11-02T19:56:12Z
    elapsed_ms: 259438281
    discovered_count: 63923
    novel_count: 22489
    duplicate_count: 30743
    queued_count: 10691
    downloaded_count: 53232
    warc_revisit_count: 30705
    warc_url_count: 53218
    total_data_in_kbs: 10417204
    duplicate_bytes: 9717010264
    warc_compressed_bytes: 355383641
    doc_rate: 0.21
    kb_rate: 40.0
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 October 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 October 30
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 October 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 November 11
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 November 12
  - not present, 2016 November 16
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 November 19
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 November 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 November 25
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 November 30
    crawl: 251965
    start_date: 2016-11-30T19:46:10Z
    original_start_date: 2016-11-30T19:46:10Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-12-03T20:22:27Z
    end_date: 2016-12-03T19:46:56Z
    elapsed_ms: 259227672
    discovered_count: 67035
    novel_count: 24992
    duplicate_count: 30985
    queued_count: 11058
    downloaded_count: 55977
    warc_revisit_count: 30947
    warc_url_count: 55964
    total_data_in_kbs: 10533159
    duplicate_bytes: 9678648930
    warc_compressed_bytes: 449892931
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 November 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 November 30
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 November 30
  - not present, 2016 December 1
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 December 1
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 December 2
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 December 4
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 December 4
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 December 30
    crawl: 257592
    start_date: 2016-12-30T19:46:02Z
    original_start_date: 2016-12-30T19:46:02Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-01-02T20:05:40Z
    end_date: 2017-01-02T19:46:35Z
    elapsed_ms: 259224045
    discovered_count: 68067
    novel_count: 20266
    duplicate_count: 36173
    queued_count: 11628
    downloaded_count: 56439
    warc_revisit_count: 36133
    warc_url_count: 56426
    total_data_in_kbs: 10580965
    duplicate_bytes: 9900131840
    warc_compressed_bytes: 365214299
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 December 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 December 31
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2016 December 31
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2017 January 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2017 January 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2017 January 26
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2017 January 29
  - not present, 2017 January 29
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2017 January 30
    crawl: 264268
    start_date: 2017-01-30T19:45:52Z
    original_start_date: 2017-01-30T19:45:52Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-02-02T21:46:05Z
    end_date: 2017-02-02T19:46:41Z
    elapsed_ms: 259234261
    discovered_count: 64278
    novel_count: 22285
    duplicate_count: 30909
    queued_count: 11084
    downloaded_count: 53194
    warc_revisit_count: 30902
    warc_url_count: 53182
    total_data_in_kbs: 10371627
    duplicate_bytes: 9677455399
    warc_compressed_bytes: 362159595
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2017 January 30
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2017 February 6
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2017 February 15
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2017 February 16
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 February 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 February 22
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 February 24
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 February 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 February 28
    crawl: 269970
    start_date: 2017-02-28T19:46:11Z
    original_start_date: 2017-02-28T19:46:11Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-03T20:01:34Z
    end_date: 2017-03-03T19:47:27Z
    elapsed_ms: 259268734
    discovered_count: 166232
    novel_count: 30070
    duplicate_count: 22551
    queued_count: 113611
    downloaded_count: 52621
    download_failures: 11
    warc_revisit_count: 22524